Guide to the National Education Association-Film, Audio, and Video records, 1938-2011 NEA1010.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Promotional Material, 1938-2011, bulk 1954-2011; 1954-2011; Series 3; 187 Linear Feet
  - Willa Cofield Johnson interview, by Al-Tony Gilmore, September 30, 2010; Series 3; Two audio tape cassettes with manuscript notes from interview. (Box 3851, Folder 5)
  - The Wired City & Those Careless Promises (Fred Friendly), undated; Series 3; Audio cassette tape (Box 4031, Folder 2)
  - Word Associations, September 15, 1997; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3985, Folder 10)
  - Word Associations - The End User is Near, September 15, 1997; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4012, Folder 6)
  - Words, February 1, 1995; Series 3; 1in magnetic tape (Box 4029, Folder 16)
  - WVEA "At Risk" PSA #1, March 6, 1992; Series 3; 1in magnetic tape (Box 4029, Folder 17)
  - "Why Self Governance for the Teaching Profession", Undated; Series (Box 3849, Film 1-inch type data_value_missing_11aa836bb7b5322fe9374213c8bfd35c)
  - You and the NEA, Undated; Series 3 (Box 3663, Folder 4)
    Separated materials found in Box 3661 File 5 2 Filmstrips
  - You and the NEA (WIthout Music) - Slide Film, October 27, 1956; Series 3; 1/4" magnetic audio tape, no speed indicated. No available equipment to play this size reel. (Box 3829, Folder 1)
  - You Are Not Alone, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3994, Folder 6)
  - Youth Wants to Know with Senator Kennedy, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3994, Folder 48)
  - Youth Wants to Know with Senator Kennedy, undated; series 3 (Box 4512, Folder 1)
  - You've Come a Long Way Baby, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3972, Folder 28)
  - YWTK Mr. Barboline, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3994, Folder 7)
  - YWTK Mr. Barboline, undated; series 3 (Box 4588, Folder 1)